quimbee.com 2019-12-07

# Privacy - Quimbee

You're using an unsupported browser. Quimbee might not work properly for you until you [update your browser](https://browsehappy.com/). 

## 1\. Introduction.

1.1. Effective Date. The effective date of this Privacy Policy is December 1, 2017. Last Updated: This Privacy Policy was last updated on August 13, 2019.

1.2. Purpose and Scope. Sellers International LLC (“Quimbee” or “Company”) is committed to respecting the privacy rights of users of the Quimbee website, the Quimbee service, and any software applications made available by Quimbee, such as any mobile-device application Quimbee makes available (together, the “Service”). Quimbee is committed to protecting personal data we may collect from visitors and any other individual or entity (“User”, “you”, or “your”) through our compliance with this privacy policy (“Privacy Policy”). 

1.3. Scope. This Privacy Policy applies to data collection by Quimbee and shall apply to your use of the publicly accessible portions of this web site at <https://www.quimbee.com/> (the “Site”) and other Quimbee-related sites, applications, software, communications, capabilities, and services (“Services”). We have established and implemented this Privacy Policy to inform you, the User of the Site, of the type of information collected by us and how we use and protect such information.

1.4. Separate Terms of Service. By using the Service, you represent and warrant that you have also read and understood, and agree to be bound by, both this Privacy Policy and Quimbee’s separate Terms of Service document (the “ **Terms of Service** ”), which is incorporated by reference and made part of this Privacy Policy. The Terms of Service document is available at <https://www.quimbee.com/about/terms>.

1.5. **_Please read this Privacy Policy carefully to understand our policies and practices regarding your information and how we will treat it. If you do not agree with our policies and practices, you may choose not to use our Site or Services. By accessing or using this Site or using our Services, you agree to this Privacy Policy. This policy may change from time to time. Your continued use of this Website or use of the Services after we make changes is deemed to be acceptance of those changes, so please check the policy periodically for updates._**

1.6. Irrespective of which country you live in, you authorize us to transfer, store, and use your information in the United States and any other country where we operate. In some of these countries, the privacy and data-protection laws and rules regarding when government authorities may access data may vary from those in the country where you live. Learn more about our data-transfer operations in the “Storage and Transfer of Information” section below. If you do not agree to the transfer, storage, and use of your information in the United States, and any other country where we operate, please do not use the Sites or Services.

## 2\. When this Privacy Policy Applies.

2.1. Quimbee’s Privacy Policy applies to all of the Services offered by Quimbee, and Services offered on our Site, but excludes services that have separate privacy policies that do not incorporate this Privacy Policy. Our Privacy Policy does not apply to services offered by other companies or individuals, including products or sites that may be displayed to you, or other sites linked from our Services. Our Privacy Policy does not cover the information practices of other companies and organizations who advertise on our Services and who may use Cookies, pixel tags, and other technologies to serve and offer relevant ads.

## 3\. Updates and Changes to Privacy Policy.

3.1. Each time you access the Service, the then-current version of this Privacy Policy will apply. Each time you use the Service, we recommend that you check the date of this Privacy Policy in Section 1.1 (Effective Date) and review any changes since the last time you used the Service.

## 4\. Children’s Privacy. 

4.1. Quimbee does not solicit or knowingly collect Personal Information from children under the age of 13. If Quimbee obtains actual knowledge that it has collected Personal Information from a child under the age of 13, Quimbee will immediately delete that information from its database. Because Quimbee does not collect Personal Information from children under the age of 13, Quimbee has no such information to use or disclose to third parties. Quimbee has designed this Privacy Policy to comply with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (“COPPA”).

## 5\. Information Collection Practices.

5.1. **Traffic Data**. Like most website and mobile-application operators, Quimbee collects information that web browsers automatically make available, including: (i) IP addresses, (ii) Internet domain names, (iii) types of devices accessing the Service, and (iv) types of Web browsers accessing the Service (collectively “ **Traffic Data** ”). Traffic Data is not meant to personally identify you, although it may be possible to identify you using Traffic Data in combination with other data.

5.2. **Cookie Policy**. “ **Cookies** ” are text files that are placed on your computer by websites that you visit or certain emails that you open. Cookies store a string of information on a user’s computer or mobile device, which the user’s web browser provides to the Service automatically each time it interacts with the Service. The purpose of Cookies is to identify the user as a unique user of the Service or to store the user’s preferences for that website. Quimbee uses two types of Cookies: “first-party Cookies” and “third-party Cookies.”

5.2.1. **First-Party Cookies.** Quimbee uses first-party Cookies on the Service for the following purposes: (1) to gather visitor and access information relevant to customizing the Service to your interests and (2) to store your user ID so you do not have to re-enter it each time you use the Service.

5.2.2. _**If you do not wish to have first-party Cookies placed on your computer or mobile device, you should set your web browser to refuse Cookies before accessing the Service. However, certain features of the Service may not function properly without the aid of Cookies. If you refuse Cookies, you assume all responsibility for any resulting loss of functionality.**_

5.2.3. **Third-Party Cookies and Advertising**.

5.2.3.1. **Advertising on Third-Party Websites**. **** Quimbee may advertise on other Third-Party Websites to you after you access the Service. We and third-party marketing partners, including without limitation Google, Inc. (“ **Google** ”), may use first-party Cookies (such as the Google Analytics Cookie), third-party Cookies (such as the DoubleClick Cookie), and web beacons (such as the Facebook conversion-tracking pixel, see <https://www.facebook.com/business/a/online-sales/conversion-tracking>), including across multiple devices, to inform, optimize, and serve advertisements to you based on your use of the Service. This practice is commonly known as retargeting or remarketing (see <https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Behavioral_retargeting>).

5.2.3.2. **Google Analytics**.

5.2.3.2.1. Google Analytics is a web analytics service that helps website and app owners understand how their visitors engage with their properties. It may use a set of Cookies to collect information and report website usage statistics without personally identifying individual visitors to Google. The main Cookie used by Google Analytics is the “__ga” Cookie. Quimbee uses Google Analytics on the Quimbee website.

5.2.4. **Opting Out of Third-Party Cookies**.

5.2.4.1. You may customize your Google Cookies preferences or opt out of using Google Cookies on the Google Ads Settings page at <http://www.google.com/settings/ads>.

5.2.4.2. You may learn about Facebook Cookies and how to customize your preferences at <https://www.facebook.com/about/ads>.

5.2.4.3. You may opt out of using other third parties’ Cookies by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative opt-out page at <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>. You can also learn more about how to delete or control Cookies at <http://www.aboutcookies.org/>.

5.3. **Third-Party Analytics Services**.

Quimbee selects Third-Party Analytics Services to help provide the Service to you; for example, Google Analytics. Quimbee only shares information with the Third Party that is required for the service they are offering and contractually bind these providers to keep any information Quimbee shares with them as confidential and to be used only for particular purposes.

5.4. **Analytics Policy and Device Ad ID Collection**.

5.4.1. Advertising IDs or “ **Device Ad ID** ”s are files that are placed on your mobile application by your device manufacturer. More information is available at <https://developer.android.com/google/play-services/id.html>. The purpose of a Device Ad ID is to identify the user as a unique user of the Service without collecting Personal Information.

5.4.2. Quimbee collects Device Ad IDs.

5.4.3. **_If you do not wish for Quimbee to access your Device Ad ID, you must inform Quimbee of your opt-out immediately, using the “Contact Us” form available through your account, and then permanently cease all use of Quimbee. If you opt out in this fashion, you assume all responsibility for any resulting loss of functionality._**

5.5. **Personally Identifiable Information**. To use certain features of the Service, you might be asked to provide Quimbee certain personally identifiable information (“ **Personal Information** ”). Personal Information includes the following categories, without limitation: (1) “ **Contact Data** ” (such as your name, phone number, fax number, mailing address, and email address); (2) “ **Financial Data** ” (such as your credit/debit card number, expiration date, and billing address); (3) “ **Demographic Data** ” (such as your law school graduation date, law school attended, and your billing ZIP code); and (4) “ **Third-Party Social Media Account Data** ” (such as your account information for third-party social media accounts when you access the Service in connection to those accounts); (5) “ **Work History Data** ” (such as your resume, including education and experience). In each case, you will be asked to provide Personal Information; the Service will not gather it secretly. Quimbee may supplement the Personal Information you provide with additional Personal Information gathered from public sources or from third parties (e.g., consumer reporting agencies) who may lawfully provide that information to Quimbee. You are under no obligation to provide Personal Information, with the caveat that your refusal to do so may prevent you from using certain features of the Service.

5.6. **Specific Information Collected**. Quimbee collects the following specific items of Personal Information:

5.6.1. your first and last name

5.6.2. your email address

5.7. **Information You Make Public**. The Service may contain features (e.g., instant messages, electronic messaging, etc.) that allow you to upload, post, transmit, display, perform, or distribute content, or other information, including your Personal Information. Any information that you choose to disclose through such features becomes public information over which Quimbee is unable to exercise control. You should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your Personal Information through these features, and you agree to assume all responsibility for doing so.

5.8. **Mobile Device Information**. **** Quimbee may collect: (i) information about the type, make, and model of your mobile device, the operating system you use on the device, browser type and specifications, the network service or wireless communication provider who connects your device to a telecommunications system or systems, your internet protocol address, and other unique identifiers assigned by third parties to your mobile device, and (ii) information about your activity on the device, including your use of other mobile applications on the same device, click data and click patterns in relation to promotional advertising on your device, Cookies (defined above), tracking tags, pixel tags, web beacons, and visitor history.

5.9. **Geolocation**. Quimbee may access and collect information regarding the physical geographic location of your computer or mobile device.

## 6\. Information Use and Disclosure Practices.

6.1. **Traffic Data and Information Gathered Using Cookies**. Quimbee analyzes Traffic Data and information gathered using Cookies to help Quimbee better understand who is using the Service and how they are using it. By identifying patterns and trends in usage, Quimbee is able to better design the Service to improve your experience and to serve you more relevant and interesting content. From time to time, Quimbee may release Traffic Data and information gathered using Cookies in the aggregate, such as by publishing a report on trends in the usage of the Service. Quimbee does not attempt to link information gathered using Cookies to Personal Information.

6.2. **Personal Information**.

6.2.1. **Generally**. **_Quimbee will NEVER sell your Personal Information to anyone_**. Quimbee uses your Contact Data to send you information about Quimbee and Quimbee’s products and services, and to contact you when necessary in connection with the Service. Quimbee uses your Financial Data to verify your qualifications for certain features of the Service and, when necessary, to bill you. Quimbee uses your Demographic Data to customize and tailor your experience on the Service. Quimbee uses your Third-Party Social Media Account Data in accordance with this Privacy Policy and the privacy policies of third-party social media companies, such as Facebook and Twitter. As with Traffic Data and information gathered using Cookies, from time to time Quimbee may release Demographic Data in the aggregate, such as by publishing a report on trends in the usage of the Service.

6.2.2. **Disclosure Practices**. Except under the following categories of circumstances, Quimbee will keep your Personal Information private and will not share it with third parties.

6.2.2.1. **Disclosure to Third-Party Partners in Connection with an Exclusive Discount or Offer**. Quimbee offers exclusive discounts and benefits to certain Third-Party Partners and their members or customers. You might claim one of those discounts and benefits, in which case Quimbee may use your Personal Information to help our Third-Party Partners better understand the demographics of our target audiences, as well as to support both the marketing of Quimbee’s products and services and our Third-Party Partner’s products and services.

6.2.2.2. **Disclosure in Connection with Service**. Quimbee discloses Personal Information to those who help it provide services, including without limitation those who perform technical, administrative, and data-processing tasks such as hosting, billing, fulfillment, data storage, and security.

6.2.2.3. **By Law or to Protect Rights**. Quimbee discloses Personal Information when required to do so by law, in response to a subpoena or court order, or when Quimbee believes in its sole discretion that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of Quimbee, third parties, or the public.

6.2.2.4. **Business Transfers; Bankruptcy**. Quimbee reserves the right to transfer all Personal Information in its possession to a successor organization in the event of a merger, acquisition, or bankruptcy or other sale of all or a portion of Quimbee’s assets. Other than to the extent ordered by a bankruptcy or other court, the use and disclosure of all transferred Personal Information will be subject to this Privacy Policy or to a new privacy policy if you are given notice of that new privacy policy and an opportunity to affirmatively opt out of it. Personal Information submitted or collected after a transfer, however, may be subject to a new privacy policy adopted by Quimbee’s successor organization.

6.2.2.5. **Unpaid Accounts**. If you fail to pay any balance owed in consideration of services, Quimbee may, as permitted by law, report your Personal Information, including without limitation your unpaid balance, to consumer credit reporting services, collection agencies, and others.

## 7\. Consent to Receive Electronic Communications From Company. 

Without limitation, by registering for the Service and/or by providing your name, email, postal or residential address, and/or phone number through the Service, you expressly consent to receive electronic and other communications from Quimbee, over the short term and periodically, including email communications, regarding the Service, new product offers, promotions, and other matters. You may opt out of receiving electronic communications at any time by (a) following the unsubscribe instructions contained in each communication or (b) sending an email to support@quimbee.com.

## 8\. Security of Personal Information.

Quimbee takes security seriously. We use commercially reasonable safeguards to protect against the unauthorized access, use, modification, destruction, or disclosure of your Personal Information. However, due to the realities of data security, Quimbee is unable to guarantee that any information provided to us will not be accessed, hacked, disclosed, altered, or destroyed by unauthorized parties.

## 9\. Lost or Stolen Information. 

You must promptly notify us if your credit, bank, other financial institution information, username, or password is lost, stolen, or used without permission. In such an event, we will remove the compromised information and update our records accordingly.

## 10\. User Ability to Access, Update, and Correct Personal Information. 

Quimbee wants your Personal Information to be complete and accurate. As stated in the Terms of Service, by using the Service, you represent and warrant that all information you provide in connection with your use of the Service is current, complete, and accurate, and that you will update that information as needed to maintain its completeness and accuracy. Subject to applicable law, you may obtain a copy of personal information we maintain about you or you may update or correct inaccuracies in that information by accessing your Settings page. To confirm the completeness and accuracy of, or make changes to, your Personal Information, visit your Settings page. Through your Settings page, you may review and update your Personal Information that we have already collected.

## 11\. Third-Party Websites. 

Quimbee neither owns nor controls Third-Party Websites. Accordingly, Third-Party Websites are under no obligation to comply with this Privacy Policy except with respect to Personal Information provided directly to them by Quimbee. Before visiting or providing Personal Information to Third-Party Websites, you should inform yourself of the privacy policies and practices (if any) of those Third-Party Websites, and you should take those steps necessary to, in your discretion, protect your privacy.

## 12\. Promotional Activities. 

By providing an email address on the Quimbee Site, you agree that we may contact you in the event of a change in this Privacy Policy, to provide you with any service-related notices, or to provide you with information about our events, invitations, or related information. From time to time, Quimbee may conduct contests, giveaways, and other promotions (collectively, “ **Promotional Activities** ”). Any information submitted in connection with Promotional Activities will be treated in accordance with this Privacy Policy. From time to time, Quimbee may also ask you to participate in surveys designed to help Quimbee improve the Service. Any Personal Information provided to Quimbee in connection with any survey will be used only in relation to that survey and will be disclosed to third parties not bound by this Privacy Policy only in aggregated form.

For purposes of this Privacy Policy, “opt-in” is generally defined as any affirmative action by a user to submit or receive information, as the case may be.

We currently provide the following opt-out opportunities: 

  1. At any time, you can follow a link provided in offers, newsletters, or other email messages (except for e-commerce confirmation or service notice emails) received from us to unsubscribe from the service.     

  2. At any time, you can contact us through email at support@quimbee.com provided below to unsubscribe from any services or to opt-out of our right per your consent under the terms of this Privacy Policy to share your Personal Information.  

Notwithstanding anything else in this Privacy Policy, please note that we always reserve the right to contact you in the event of a change in this Privacy Policy, or to provide you with any service-related notices. 

## 12\. Storage and Transfer of Information.

We may, directly or indirectly through third-party entities around the world, process, store, and transfer all of the information you provide, including your personal information, as described in this Privacy Policy. Specifically, the information and personal information that we collect from you may be transferred to, and stored in a country with laws which are different, and potentially not as protective, as the laws of your own country.  By submitting your information and personal information and using the Site, you agree to this transfer, storing, or processing. We will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your personal information is treated securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy. 

## 13\. Business Transitions. 

In the event Quimbee goes through a business transition, including without limitation any merger, acquisition, partnership, business reorganization, debt finance, or sale of company assets, or in the event of an insolvency, bankruptcy, or receivership (together a “ **Business Transition** ”), Quimbee may use information collected in accordance with this Privacy Policy and subject to its restrictions, as part of any such Business Transition. In such instances, your information can be part of the assets transferred.

## 14\. Your California Privacy Rights. 

California Civil Code Section § 1798.83 permits Users of our Site that are California residents to request certain information regarding our disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please write to us at the address listed in the How to Contact Us section below.  We do not disclose personal information to third parties for the third parties’ direct marketing purposes.

## 15\. Do-Not-Track Disclosure. 

Quimbee does not respond to “Do Not Track” signals sent by browsers.

## 16\. How We Protect Personal Information. 

Quimbee maintains administrative, technical, and physical safeguards designed to protect the User's Personal Information and information against accidental, unlawful, or unauthorized destruction, loss, alteration, access, disclosure, or use. We implement appropriate technical and organizational measures to ensure a level of security appropriate to the risk, taking into account technological reality, cost, the scope, context, and purposes of processing weighted against the severity and likelihood that the processing could threaten individual rights and freedoms. For example, we engage third-party data storage providers who utilize commercially reasonable security measures such as encryption, firewalls, and transport layer security (TLS) or hypertext transfer protocol secure (HTTPS) to protect Personal Information.

## 17\. How to Contact Us. 

If you have any specific questions about this Privacy Policy, you can contact us via email at the address below:

Send e-mail to: privacy@quimbee.com
